{
    "id": "267573f45c1d490daf225f8d52a8c332",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You will not succeed …………………………. you work really hard.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "in case"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57e771086d0b4fdd8e8ac25a8e058407"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have worked in this office ………………………… twenty years.",
            "description": "Use for with duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55a598f158134cf3a18fa212e1f18cd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ……………………………… poisoning her cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af10cee07c15488088aa8b7c0505407e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left ten minutes …………………………..",
            "description": "Ago is used to count back from the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f63453cc1c84f55acb33ee1bf54a9d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you follow your doctor’s advice, you will get well soon.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20bdd0dfb94e4fe3ae72f72c9ca40b64"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martha along with her friends ……………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "When two nouns are connected with and, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37478f4ec2c64d26a8ad0e4b66f19d9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "What …………………………. you do then?",
            "description": "The word then shows distance in time. Hence, a past tense is used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa58510df83f4d60b10792231036b551"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy has been missing …………………….. Monday.",
            "description": "Use since with the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7913dc0f5774ec89759f6451a2a8276"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………………. a hot day, I didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being",
                "was",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "787403958b6a4b4da2fc79fb7c6e8e34"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the hens ……………………………… missing.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d4862a9af214d88a74caf641661faa5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither John nor his wife ………………………… there.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after neither/nor.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c4e4ff2aa3d4aa2b988cf2e440f9f60"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is collecting money for …………………………..",
            "description": "The homeless means all homeless people.",
            "answers": [
                "homeless",
                "the homeless",
                "homeless people"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3193ec8737eb427a9de3574e756f5475"
        }
    ]
}